Guide to the Vice President for Finance and Administration Records, 1819-2017
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series I. James Ritterskamp Files, 1966-1981
  - New Long Range, 1977 (Box 27)
  - College: Grants – General, 1979-1981 (Box 27)
  - College: Grants – Dept of Energy Grant to Robert L. Stearns, 1977-1981 (Box 27)
  - College: Energy Grants and Programs, 1978-1980 (Box 27)
  - College: Esso Education Foundation (SPUR), 1970 (Box 27)
  - College: Ford Foundation Grant, 1969-1970 (Box 27)
  - Federal and State – Student Financial Aid Educational Opportunity Grants, 1970-1979 (Box 27)
  - Student Financial Aid: Federal Insured Student Loan Program, undated (Box 27)
  - Federal – Student Financial Aid Programs, 1976-1980 (Box 27)
  - College: Student Financial Aid National Direct Student Program, 1973-1979 (Box 28)
  - Federal: Student Financial Aid National Defense Student Loan Program, 1967-1972 (Box 28)
  - Federal: Student Financial Aid Work Study Program, 1969-1980 (Box 28)
  - College: NSF Institutional Grant, 1968-1974 (Box 28)
  - College: Student Loans – Collection Agencies, 1978 (Box 28)
  - College: Student Loans – Problems, 1978-1980 (Box 28)
  - Student Loans – Sallie Mae, 1973-1976 (Box 28)
  - Insurance: Art Department, 1970-1978 (Box 28)
  - Insurance: Library, 1970-1978 (Box 28)
  - College Insurance, 1978-1981 (Box 28)
  - Insurance – Mario Domandi, 1978-1980 (Box 28)
  - College Insurance – Helen Miringoff (Pension), 1979-1981 (Box 28)
  - Insurance: Malpractice Insurance, 1974-1976 (Box 28)
  - National Student Services, Inc., 1975 (Box 28)
  - Insurance Special Collections, 1974-1975 (Box 28)
  - College – Insurance – Students, 1968-1980 (Box 28)
  - Insurance: Trustees and Officers, AAVC Directors, 1972-1980 (Box 28)
  - Insurance: Unemployment Insurance, 1970-1981 (Box 28)
  - College – Faculty – Benefits, 1967-1979 (Box 28)
  - Faculty General, 1976-1980 (Box 28)
  - Faculty Contracts, 1972-1977 (Box 28)
  - College: Faculty – Leave System, 1968-1973 (Box 28)
  - Faculty – Early Retirement, 1973-1976 (Box 28)
  - College – Retirement and Pension, 1968-1980 (Box 28)
  - College – Union: Contracts and Negotiations, 1969 (Box 28)
  - College – Union: Correspondence, undated (Box 28)
  - Union Negotiations, 1980-1981 (Box 28)
  - College Union Negotiations, 1970-1976 (Box 28)
  - College: Union Negotiations June 1968 (Box 29)
  - College: Union (Minutes of) Labor – Management Committee, 1969-1980 (Box 29)
  - College: National Labor Relations Board – Report, 1970-1972 (Box 29)
  - College: Union – Welfare Fund, 1979-1980 (Box 29)
  - College: Union Agreement, undated (Box 29)
  - College: Union – Collective Bargaining in Higher Education, 1972-1976 (Box 29)
  - Board Actions, 1975 (Box 29)
  - Poughkeepsie Journal 11/20/1967 (Box 29)
  - Trustees: Allocations Committee, 1971-1973 (Box 29)
  - Responsibilities of Trustees, 1972-1974 (Box 29)
  - Current Board FPCC Discussion, 1976 (Box 29)
  - Trustees: Audit Committee, undated (Box 29)
  - Trustees: By-Laws, 1970-1973 (Box 29)
  - Budget Committee, 1975-1980 (Box 29)
  - JJR File – Buildings and Grounds: Parking Area, 1968 (Box 29)
  - Trustees: Buildings and Grounds: Committee, 1979-1981 (Box 29)
  - Trustees: Buildings and Grounds: Committee, 1975-1978 (Box 29)
  - Trustees: Buildings and Grounds: Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 29)
  - Trustees: Buildings and Grounds: Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 29)
  - Trustees: Committee on Budget, 1980-1981 (Box 29)
  - Trustees: Committee on Budget, 1979-1980 (Box 29)
  - Trustees: Committee on Budget, 1978-1979 (Box 29)
  - Trustees: Committee on Budget, 1977-1978 (Box 29)
  - Trustees: Committee on Budget Minutes, 1977-1978 (Box 29)
  - Trustees: Subcommittee on Budget, 1975 (Box 29)
  - Trustees: Committee on Budget Minutes, 1979-1980 (Box 29)
  - Trustees: Committee on Budget, 1976-1977 (Box 29)
  - Trustees: Committee on Budget, 1975-1976 (Box 29)
  - Trustees: Committee on Budget, 1974-1975 (Box 29)
  - Trustees: Committee on Budget Minutes, 1972-1977 (Box 29)
  - Trustees: Budget Workshop, 1972-1973 (Box 29)
  - Trustees: Coeducation Committee, 1973-1975 (Box 29)
  - Trustees: Development Policy Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 29)
  - Trustees: Executive Committee, 1975-1981 (Box 29)
  - Trustees: Subcommittee of the Executive Committee, 1974 (Box 29)
  - Trustees: General Information, 1976-1977 (Box 29)
  - Trustees: General Information, 1977-1981 (Box 29)
  - Trustees: Committee on Investor Responsibility (IRC), 1979 (Box 30)
  - Trustees: Investments and Finance Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 30)
  - Trustees: Investments and Finance Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 30)
  - Trustees: Committee on Investments and Finance, 1977-1978 (Box 30)
  - Trustees: Investments and Finance Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 30)
  - Trustees: Committee on Investments and Finance, 1976-1977 (Box 30)
  - Trustees: Investments and Finance - Seatrain Lines, Inc., 1978-1980 (Box 30)
  - Trustees: Investments and Finance Committee – Report on Procedure in Handling of Securities, undated (Box 30)
  - Trustees: Joint Committee on Coordinate Fund-Raising, 1974 (Box 30)
  - Trustees: Personnel Committee, 1976-1980 (Box 30)
  - Trustees: Reports of Vice President for Administration, 1977-1981 (Box 30)
  - Investment Committee Material, 1979 (Box 30)
  - Arterial, 1978 (Box 30)
  - State: McGeorge Bundy Plan (Governor’s Committee on Higher Education), 1967-1968 (Box 30)
  - State: Civil Defense Commissions, 1970-1971 (Box 30)
  - State: Commission on Independent Colleges and Universities, 1972-1980 (Box 30)
  - State: CICU City Center, NYC, 1971-1976 (Box 30)
  - State: Commission on Independent Colleges and Universities – Annual Meeting, 1972 (Box 30)
  - State: Commission on Independent Colleges and Universities 1972 Statewide Master Plan, 1972-1973 (Box 30)
  - State: Legislation – Representatives, 1975 (Box 30)
  - State: Letters to Representatives, 1972 (Box 30)
  - State: Department of Social Services, 1976 (Box 30)
  - State: New York State Board of Social Welfare, 1976 (Box 30)
  - State: Senate Legislative Report, 1968-1969 (Box 30)
  - State: State Education Department Anti-Hazing, undated (Box 30)
  - State: State Aid for Private Colleges, 1968-1978 (Box 30)
  - State: Dormitory Authority, undated (Box 30)
  - State: State Education Department, 1978 (Box 30)
  - State: State Education Department General Information Survey, 1968-1969 (Box 30)
  - State: State Education Department Institute Grant Subsidy, 1970-1971 (Box 30)
  - State: HEW Compliance Reports, undated (Box 30)
  - State: State Education Department General Information Survey, 1969-1970 (Box 31)
  - State: State Education Department – HEW Physical Facilities Report, 1978 (Box 31)
  - State: State Education Dept Application Under Title VI Higher Education Act of 1965, 1971-1976 (Box 31)
  - State: State Education Department – HEOP, 1970-1979 (Box 31)
  - State: State Education Department Regents Planning Documents, 1971 (Box 31)
  - State: State Education Department 1978 Progress Report (Box 31)
  - State: State Education Department Report, 1973-1978 (Box 31)
  - State: State Education Department SHAPE, 1971 (Box 31)
  - State: Education Law – Article 129-A, 1969 (Box 31)
  - State: Tap Certification, 1980 (Box 31)
  - State: Regents 1980 Statewide Plan (Box 31)
  - State: State Aid for Private Colleges, 1979-1981 (Box 31)
  - American Council on Education, undated (Box 31)
  - Federal: Association of American Colleges, 1968-1981 (Box 31)
  - Federal: Committee for Full Funding of Education Program, 1973 (Box 31)
  - Federal: Federal Funds Received, 1973 (Box 31)
  - Federal: Funding Available for Facilities and Construction, 1969-1971 (Box 31)
  - Financing: Bio Sciences HEW, 1968-1981 (Box 31)
  - Federal: Department of Health Education and Welfare, 1966-1977 (Box 31)
  - Analysis of Facilities and Recommendations for Access for the Handicapped, 1978 (Box 31)
  - Federal: HEW – Rehabilitation Act of 1973 – Handrails, 1973-1979 (Box 31)
  - Federal: HEW – Nondiscrimination on the Basis of Handicap Rehabilitation Act of 1973, 1973-1980 (Box 31)
  - Federal: HEW Title VI – Information and Correspondence, 1970 (Box 31)
  - Federal: HEW Rehabilitation Act of 1973 – Access for the Handicapped, 1979-1981 (Box 31)
  - Federal: HEW Special Services Grant, 1977-1980 (Box 31)
  - Federal: HEW – Title IV Education Amendments of 1972, 1975-1979 (Box 31)
  - Federal: Legislation, 1971-1977 (Box 31)
  - National Register of Historical Places, 1979 (Box 31)
  - Federal: National Association of Independent Colleges and Universities, 1978 (Box 31)
  - Federal: National Association Report on Salaries, 1969-1970 (Box 31)
  - Federal: National Institutes of Health, 1968-1980 (Box 31)
  - Federal: National Labor Relations Board, 1970 (Box 31)
  - Federal: National Science Foundation, 1973-1981 (Box 31)
  - Federal: US Civil Service Commission, 1966-1972 (Box 31)
  - Federal: US Dept of Justice Educational Development Program, 1971 (Box 31)
  - Federal: US Dept of Labor, 1977-1979 (Box 31)
  - College: Tax Information, 1969-1972 (Box 32)
  - College: Departments – Art, 1968-1981 (Box 32)
  - College: Computer Center, 1977-1981 (Box 32)
  - College: Computer Use, 1980 (Box 32)
  - Computer Center: IBM 4341 Data Processing System, 1978-1979 (Box 32)
  - College: Computer Upgrade, 1973-1977 (Box 32)
  - Computer Center: Systems Analyst, 1976-1979 (Box 32)
  - Computer Center 4341 Processor, undated (Box 32)
  - Departments: Biology, 1969-1980 (Box 32)
  - College: Departments – Chapel and Chaplain’s Office, 1968-1981 (Box 32)
  - Computer Center – IBM Agreements, 1965-1968 (Box 32)
  - College: Departments: Classics, 1974-1979 (Box 32)
  - College: Departments: Drama Film Workshop, 1969-1979 (Box 32)
  - College: Departments: Education, 1976 (Box 32)
  - College: Departments: English, 1969-1977 (Box 32)
  - College: Field Work Office (Off-Campus Studies), 1968-1981 (Box 32)
  - College: Departments: Health – Baldwin House, 1967-1980 (Box 32)
  - College: Departments: Health Service Reports, 1968-1969 (Box 32)
  - College: Departments: Health Counseling Service, 1980 (Box 32)
  - College: Departments: History, 1977 (Box 32)
  - College: Departments: Languages, 1968-1980 (Box 32)
  - College: Departments: Library, 1969-1981 (Box 32)
  - College: Departments: Lockwood Library, 1977-1978 (Box 32)
  - College: Departments: Mathematics, 1971 (Box 32)
  - College: Departments: Music, 1969-1980 (Box 33)
  - College: Departments: Philosophy, 1969-1972 (Box 33)
  - College: Departments: Physical Education, 1968-1980 (Box 33)
  - College: Departments: Physics Astronomy, 1967-1979 (Box 33)
  - College: Programs – East Asian Studies, 1968-1975 (Box 33)
  - College: Programs – Science, Technology and Society (STS), 197-1977 (Box 33)
  - College: Programs – Wilderness Workshop, 1977 (Box 33)
  - College: Departments: Psychology (Film Program), 1968-1980 (Box 33)
  - College: Purchasing Department, 1969-1981 (Box 33)
  - College: Departments: Registrar, 1969-1981 (Box 33)
  - College: Departments: Science, 1969-1979 (Box 33)
  - College: Departments: Social Science, 1972-1977 (Box 33)
  - College: Students – Cardinal Puff, 1978 (Box 33)
  - Students: Check Cashing, 1970-1974 (Box 33)
  - Johnson, Jeri, 1977 (Box 33)
  - Students: Coalition for Social Responsibility, 1978-1979 (Box 33)
  - College: Students: Complaints, 1969-1981 (Box 33)
  - College: Students: Moratorium, 1969 (Box 33)
  - College: Students: Counseling Services, 1967-1975 (Box 33)
  - College: Students: Curriculum Records, 1969 (Box 33)
  - College: Students: Petitions Demonstrations SDS, 1968-1972 (Box 33)
  - College: Demonstrations – Black Sit-in, 1969 (Box 33)
  - College: Students: Employment, 1967-1978 (Box 33)
  - Students: Student Entertainment Committee, 1972-1979 (Box 33)
  - College: Students: Fines, 1971-1979 (Box 33)
  - College: Students: Fines, 1971 (Box 33)
  - College: Students: Housing, 1969-1976 (Box 33)
  - Students: Miscellany News – Correspondence, 1968-1974 (Box 33)
  - Students: New York Public Interest Research Group, Inc. (NYPIRG), 1978 (Box 33)
  - Students: Student Patrol, 1972-1980 (Box 33)
  - College: Students: Social Regulations, 1968-1970 (Box 33)
  - College: Students: Student Union, 1968 (Box 33)
  - College: Students: Transportation, 1968-1973 (Box 33)
  - College: Vassar Student Association, 1979-1980 (Box 33)
  - College: Students: Student Handbook and Directory, 1971-1979 (Box 33)
  - Committees: Campus Committee on Investor Responsibility, 1971-1980 (Box 33)
  - College: Black Studies Program Correspondence, 1969 (Box 33)
  - JJR – Buildings and Grounds, 1965-1966 (Box 33)
  - Trustees: Miscellaneous Reports, etc., 1966-1975 (Box 33)
  - Trustees: Miscellaneous Reports, etc., 1976-1979 (Box 34)
  - Trustees: Nelson Report, 1975 (Box 34)
  - Trustees: Vice President's Reports to Trustees, 1986-1992 (Box 34)
  - Comptroller's Reports, 1957-1988 (Box 34)
  - College: Mid-Hudson Graduate Center, 1969-1972 (Box 35)
- Series II. Anthony Stellato Files, 1983-2000
  - AAVC, 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Academy for Ed. Dec., 1982-1986 (Box 1)
  - Academic Computer Center, 1981-1986 (Box 1)
  - Academic Program Development, 1981-1985 (Box 1)
  - Academic Program Development, 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - ADA, 1982-1983 (Box 1)
  - Administrative Leaves, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Administrative Retreat, 1980-1987 (Box 1)
  - Admissions, 1980-1991 (Box 1)
  - Africana Studies Endowment, 1983 (Box 1)
  - Alumnae House, 1991 (Box 1)
  - Alumnae House, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Alumnae House Alterations, 1981-1982 (Box 2)
  - American Council on Education, 1980 (Box 2)
  - Amrita Club, 1983-1991 (Box 2)
  - Amrita Club, 1983-1991 (Box 2)
  - Amrita Club, 1983-1991 (Box 2)
  - Aposporos and Son, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Arlington Fire District Engine Co #1, 1983 (Box 2)
  - Analytic Investment Management Inc., 1981-1987 (Box 2)
  - Audio-Visual Department, 1981-1993 (Box 2)
  - Audit Committee, 1981-1989 (Box 2)
  - Banner, 1993-1998 (Box 2)
  - Bank Custodian, 1984 (Box 2)
  - Bank of New York, 1994 (Box 2)
  - Bankers Trust Company, 1987-1990 (Box 2)
  - Barnes, Amy, 1987-1988 (Box 2)
  - Benefits Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 3)
  - Benefits Committee, 1992-1995 (Box 3)
  - Benefits Committee, 1988-1993 (Box 3)
  - Biology Department, 1981-1990 (Box 3)
  - Black College Exchange, 1980-1990 (Box 3)
  - Borthwick, Sid, 1985-1987 (Box 3)
  - Borthwick, Sid, 1984-1985 (Box 3)
  - Borthwick, Sid, 1981-1983 (Box 4)
  - Bridge, John, 1975-1983 (Box 4)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1996 (Box 4)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1996-1997 (Box 4)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1994-1997 (Box 4)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1991-1994 (Box 4)
  - Burroughs Journals, 1954-1981 (Box 4)
  - Bursar, 1981-1985 (Box 4)
  - Campus Activities Office, 1982-1983 (Box 4)
  - Campus Communications, 1993-1994 (Box 4)
  - Campus Master Planning Committee, 1985-1989 (Box 4)
  - Campus Master Planning Committee, 1971-1984 (Box 4)
  - Campus Master Planning Committee, "Classroom Master Plan, Vol. 1,", 1999 Jul (Box 35)
  - Campus Master Planning Committee, "Classroom Master Plan, Vol. 2,", 1999 Jul (Box 35)
  - Campus Master Planning Committee, "Classroom Master Plan, Vol. 3,", 1999 Jul (Box 35)
  - Campus Master Planning Committee, "Classroom Master Plan, Vol. 4,", 1999 Jul (Box 35)
  - Career Planning, 1983 (Box 5)
  - Case, 1972-1992 (Box 5)
  - Centerbrook, 1986-1989 (Box 5)
  - Chaplain, 1959-1991 (Box 5)
  - Chemistry Department, 1977-1994 (Box 5)
  - Chicago Hall, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Chicago Hall Language Lab, 1984-1988 (Box 5)
  - Commission on Higher Education, 1984-2001 (Box 5)
  - Controllers, 1995-1997 (Box 5)
  - Controllers, 1992-1995 (Box 5)
  - Controllers, 1989-1992 (Box 5)
  - Controllers, 1981-1989 (Box 5)
  - Computer Center, 1980-1993 (Box 6)
  - Computer Center Renovations, 1994 (Box 6)
  - Computer Committee, 1981-1987 (Box 6)
  - Computer Store, 1987 (Box 6)
  - Conferences and Summer Programs, 1985-1988 (Box 6)
  - Connecticut General, 1981 (Box 6)
  - Contingency Fund, 1981-1985 (Box 6)
  - Cool, Ken, 1987-1994 (Box 6)
  - Cooperative Bookshop, 1985-1998 (Box 6)
  - Coopers and Lybrand, 1992-1994 (Box 6)
  - Coopers and Lybrand, 1990-1992 (Box 6)
  - Coopers and Lybrand, 1981-1990 (Box 6)
  - Copy Center, 1991 (Box 7)
  - Copy Machines, 1981 (Box 7)
  - CPC, 1985-1982 (Box 7)
  - Coradian, 1981-1982 (Box 7)
  - Crimmins, Charles M., 1987-1989 (Box 7)
  - Dean of the College, 1986-1994 (Box 7)
  - Dean's Office, 1980-1985 (Box 7)
  - Development, 1995-1997 (Box 7)
  - Development, 1991-1995 (Box 7)
  - Development, 1987-1994 (Box 8)
  - Development, 1987-1993 (Box 8)
  - Development, 1983-1986 (Box 8)
  - Development, 1980-1984 (Box 8)
  - Development-Capital Campaign, 1992-1996 (Box 8)
  - Development-Capital Campaign, 1991-1992 (Box 8)
  - Development Gifts, 1992-1994 (Box 8)
  - Directions, undated (Box 8)
  - Drama Department Obesity Project, 1980 (Box 8)
  - Dutchess Community College, 1995 (Box 8)
  - EACUBO, 1985-1989 (Box 8)
  - Early Retirement (Faculty), 1982-1996 (Box 9)
  - Economics Department, 1982 (Box 9)
  - Energy, 1974-1982 (Box 9)
  - Energy Committee, 1975-1981 (Box 9)
  - Energy Grant, 1981-1986 (Box 9)
  - Energy Task Force, 1982-1983 (Box 9)
  - ERTA, 1982 (Box 9)
  - Executive Director Search, 1984 (Box 9)
  - EZE, 1990-1993 (Box 9)
  - EZE, 1989-1990 (Box 9)
  - EZE, 1988-1989 (Box 9)
  - EZE, 1973-1985 (Box 9)
  - EZE, 1985-1987 (Box 10)
  - Facilities Operation, 1990-1992 (Box 10)
  - Facilities Operation, 1989-1990 (Box 10)
  - Facilities Operation, 1987-1988 (Box 10)
  - Facilities Operation, 1985-1986 (Box 10)
  - Facilities Operation, 1980-1984 (Box 10)
  - Facilities Planning, 1992-1993 (Box 10)
  - Faculty Appointments and Salary, 1983-1984 (Box 11)
  - Faculty Committees, 1982-1984 (Box 11)
  - Faculty Condos, 1990 (Box 11)
  - Faculty Housing, 1976-1999 (Box 11)
  - Faculty Housing Heat, 1974-1988 (Box 11)
  - Faculty Salary Schedule, 1980-1983 (Box 11)
  - Faculty Salary Survey, 1983-1987 (Box 11)
  - Family Medical Leave Act, 1993 (Box 11)
  - Field Work, 1986-1987 (Box 11)
  - Financial Aid, 1994-1997 (Box 11)
  - Financial Aid, 1980-1995 (Box 11)
  - FIPSE, 1981 (Box 11)
  - Fire Legislation, 1969-1983 (Box 11)
  - Fire Safety, 1984-1991 (Box 11)
  - Food Service, 1982 (Box 11)
  - Forward Planning and Priorities Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 11)
  - Foster (Johnson) Higgins, 1980-1992 (Box 11)
  - Foster (Johnson) Higgins, 1986-1993 (Box 12)
  - FPCC, 1979-1997 (Box 12)
  - French Intern, 1987 (Box 12)
  - Gifts and Estate Taxes, 1981 (Box 12)
  - Goodfellowship Club House, 1974-1994 (Box 12)
  - Grants Council, 1989-1991 (Box 12)
  - Guaranteed Student Loan Program, 1980 (Box 12)
  - Halls, 1981-1991 (Box 12)
  - Handel Group, Inc, 1982-1986 (Box 12)
  - Handicap, 1981-1989 (Box 12)
  - Harris, Brian, 1991-1998 (Box 12)
  - Hazardous Waste, 1974-1987 (Box 12)
  - Head House at Skinner Greenhouse, 1983-1984 (Box 12)
  - Heds and Beds, 1989-1996 (Box 12)
  - Hegis Financial, 1981-1988 (Box 12)
  - Heiniein Fund, 1982-1983 (Box 12)
  - Higher Education and American Philanthropy, 1981-1982 (Box 12)
  - Horoschak, 1979-1984 (Box 13)
  - House Fellows, 1982-1989 (Box 13)
  - IBM Grant, 1990-1993 (Box 13)
  - Inter-Cultural Center, 1989-1991 (Box 13)
  - Investments and Finance Committee, 1980-1982 (Box 13)
  - Investments and Finance Committee, 1983-1991 (Box 13)
  - Investments and Finance Committee, 1980-1984 (Box 13)
  - Investments and Finance Committee, 1984 (Box 13)
  - IPEDS, 1988-2000 (Box 13)
  - IRS, 1992 (Box 13)
  - IRS Form 5500, 1976-1978 (Box 13)
  - Jade Sale, 1980-1983 (Box 13)
  - James, Fred S., 1987 (Box 13)
  - Johnson, Lee, 1981-1983 (Box 13)
  - Junior Year Abroad, 1996-1997 (Box 13)
  - Kenan Fund, 1979-1991 (Box 13)
  - Kresge Foundation, 1981-1987 (Box 13)
  - Labor Management Committee, 1981-1991 (Box 13)
  - Lewis, Miles, 1983-1984 (Box 13)
  - Lewis, Miles, 1980-1983 (Box 14)
  - Liberty Mutual, 1980-1988 (Box 14)
  - Library Adriance, 1984-1997 (Box 14)
  - Liquor License, 1981-1986 (Box 14)
  - Loan Program, 1991-1995 (Box 14)
  - Loewenthal, Michael, 1990-1992 (Box 14)
  - Long Term Dept Terrace Apartments, 1982 (Box 14)
  - Main, 1985-1989 (Box 14)
  - Marine Midland Bank, 1981-1991 (Box 14)
  - McCarthy Papers, 1985 (Box 14)
  - Mellon Funds, 1980 (Box 14)
  - Mellon Grants, 1980-1988 (Box 14)
  - Middle States, 1985-1988 (Box 14)
  - Middle States, 1979-1985 (Box 14)
  - Milbank, Tweed, 1990-1995 (Box 14)
  - Milbank, Tweed, Hadley and McCloy, 1982-1989 (Box 15)
  - Milbank, Tweed, Hadley and McCloy, 1980-1987 (Box 15)
  - Moll, Richard, 1995-1998 (Box 15)
  - MONY, 1991 (Box 15)
  - MONY, 1980-1991 (Box 15)
  - MONY, 1986-1988 (Box 15)
  - Morgan, Bryant, 1989-1994 (Box 15)
  - MUDD Foundation, 1983-1985 (Box 15)
  - Murphy Farmhouse, 1982-1984 (Box 15)
  - Music Department, 1983-1990 (Box 15)
  - NACUBO, 1982-1988 (Box 15)
  - New Era, 1996-1997 (Box 16)
  - New York State Energy, 1981-1991 (Box 16)
  - New York State Dormitory Authority, 1980-1990 (Box 16)
  - New York State Inventory College and University Phys. Facilities, 1982-1986 (Box 16)
  - New York State of Master Plan, 1974-1984 (Box 16)
  - New York State of Master Plan, 1982-1988 (Box 16)
  - New York State Self Evaluation, 1983-1988 (Box 16)
  - New York State of TAP, 1980-1987 (Box 16)
  - NYSDOT Property Fishkill Plains, 1981-1987 (Box 16)
  - NYS (General), 1982-1995 (Box 16)
  - New York State of Insurance Dept, 1980-1982 (Box 16)
  - Observatory, 1987-1992 (Box 16)
  - The Olmstead Heritage Landscapes Act, 1986-1987 (Box 16)
  - Parent Loan Program, 1990 (Box 16)
  - Parking, 1984-1992 (Box 16)
  - Peat Marwick, 1987-1995 (Box 17)
  - Peat Marwick, 1983-1986 (Box 17)
  - Peat Marwick, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Personal Financial Planning Institute, 1984-1985 (Box 17)
  - Personnel, 1985-1997 (Box 17)
  - Personnel, 1979-1985 (Box 17)
  - Positions, 1980-1998 (Box 18)
  - Poughkeepsie, City of, 1990-1992 (Box 18)
  - Poughkeepsie Day School, 1963-2001 (Box 18)
  - Poughkeepsie Day School, 1969-1988 (Box 18)
  - Poughkeepsie Day School Investment Committee, 1986-1989 (Box 18)
  - Powerhouse Theater Renovations, 1984-1985 (Box 18)
  - Purchasing, 1986 (Box 18)
  - Refund Policy, 1981-1982 (Box 18)
  - Residence Office, 1982-1992 (Box 18)
  - Ritterskamp, J.J., 1981 (Box 18)
  - Saint Francis Hospital Day Care Center, 1992 (Box 18)
  - Sarcophagus—Roman, 1982 (Box 18)
  - Seven (7) College Conference, 1996 (Box 18)
  - Sloan Proposal, 1982-1989 (Box 18)
  - Staff Association, 1979-1985 (Box 18)
  - Stec, Paul, 1956-1985 (Box 18)
  - Student Insurance, 1980-1985 (Box 19)
  - Sunrise Lane, 1972-1989 (Box 19)
  - Sunset Lake, 1976-1981 (Box 19)
  - TEG, 1985-1986 (Box 19)
  - TIAA Disability, 1979-1988 (Box 19)
  - TIAA Major Medical, 1981 (Box 19)
  - TIAA Retirement, 1980-1990 (Box 19)
  - TORRENS, 1988-1989 (Box 19)
  - Toxic Waste, 1985-1988 (Box 19)
  - Tuition and Fees, 1981-1992 (Box 19)
  - U.S. Department of Education, 1980-1981 (Box 19)
  - U.S. Department of Energy, 1982-1985 (Box 19)
  - Yoder, Jay, 1998-2000 (Box 19)
- Series III. 2025 Addition, 1819-2017
  - Property Records, 1819-2017
    - Contracts - Amerada Hess Corporation, 1973-1981 (Folder 36.1)
    - Contracts - Broadcast Music, Inc., 1941 Oct 16 (Folder 36.2)
    - Contracts - Pipe Organs, 1963, 1965 (Folder 36.3)
    - Contracts - Poughkeepsie Cablevision, 1973, 1976 (Folder 36.4)
    - Contracts - Technology, 1974-1983 (Folder 36.5)
    - Correspondence - Our Lady of Lourdes High School, 2001-2004 (Folder 36.6)
    - Deeds - Abstract of Title, Vassar College land deeds through 1959, 1964; [typescripts] (Folder 36.7)
    - Deeds - Allen and Terwilliger to Vassar College, 1927 Oct 3; [1 item] (Folder 36.8)